

### **Personal Information**

Age: 23

Gender: Male

#### Contact

Phone:

922956461

Email:

awokedejenie@gmail.com

Address:

Addis Ababa

# Language Skills

Amharic - Native, English - Intermediate

# **Awoke Dejenie**

Student

#### **About**

I am Awoke Dejenie form Addis Ababa university in bachelor's degree of information system. I have joined in 2020/21 and will graduate in in 2024. I in those year have own profile like software development, network administer, Databa design and other soft skill. I have my own strength like punctuation, communication and emphasize indeed I have some weakness like anger when friends late on punctuation, and little time management.

#### **Education**

Bachelor

Information System Addis Ababa University GPA: 3.90

Jul 2024 Graduation date

## Work experience



Nov 2023 - Present 0 month

> **Software** development internship

Oct 2023 - Present

 $0 \; month \;$ 

Clup tech for social science

🖵 Jul 2023 - Sep 2023 2 month

Intern

Poshak software development campaign

I am now work at this software development campaign with my team as developer.in this intern we have given dedicated time to develop one project.

in this year I am the accountant of tech for social science Club located in Addis Ababa university FBE campus

I have work as software developer at Poshak campaign in summer. at that time, I have updated the current software as it is the startup it has some issue that I customize.

## **Certifications**

Mar 2023 Certification was issued

Mar 2022 Certification was issued

Feb 2022 Certification was issued

Oct 2021 Certification was issued China-Ethioppia Freindshiop

Embassy of the P.R of China in Ethiopia

**International Innovation** 

Hindu and wollo university technology team

**Hult Prize** 

Hult prize of Addia Ababa university

**VSO** 

**derej**ä Generated by dereja.com Inclusion and gender career development of Addis Ababa University

# **Extracurricular Activity**

Oct 2023 - Nov 2023
Accountant
Tech for socail

I am accountant of the tech for social science club

# **Additional Skills**

 $website, database\ design, network\ installation, system\ analysis\ and\ design$ 

## References

science

Addis Ababa University Instructor Addis Ababa University Lemlem Hagoss

Contact detail: lemlem.hagos@aau.edu.et